dunhilltraveldeals.com 2019-06-12

# Privacy Policy | Dunhill Travel Deals Website

**Updated As Of May 23, 2018  
**  
Dunhill Travel Deals publishes travel deals and information on its websites, mobile sites and via its opt-in email newsletters. We value our relationship with our community and respect member’s privacy. This policy is available to help you understand the handling of your personal information. We have updated some content and added details with the objective of making our practices more transparent and explain our approach to achieving GDPR compliance for ourselves and for you. Notable updates include: 

  * Greater Transparency. The new policy provides more detailed explanations of what personal information we collect, how we collect it, what we use it for, and who we share it with.
  * More User Control. The new policy also outlines specific procedures for asking us to limit or stop using your personal information.

### What Personal Information We Collect:

Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable and not otherwise publicly available. We may collect your name, email address, zip code, and travel preferences. We also monitor your activity on our site and in our newsletters.

### How We Collect Personal Information:

Dunhill Travel Deals collects personal information in a variety of ways, including when you subscribe to newsletters, when you register on or visit our website, or the websites of certain partners, and when you enter sweepstakes sponsored by Dunhill Travel Deals. We combine the data collected across these services and across your devices. Dunhill Travel Deals operates several websites featuring travel-related content and services. We may share personal information collected across these websites to better serve you.

### Use of Personal Information:

Dunhill Travel Deals only asks for personal information if it’s needed to provide a service and we then use it to deliver the most relevant, personalized content. This information will not be sold to third parties. We do not share data outside our family of brands, unless compelled by law. 

Registration is not required in order to use this site. If you do register, and in the process provide us with personally identifiable information, no information will be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.

We also provide the opportunity to receive email communications from us. In this case, we ask for personally identifiable information. We may use personal information collected to send out targeted email promotions on behalf of advertisers and industry partners. These communications will include some or all of the following: newsletters, company updates, and other relevant promotions.

### Control Over Personal Information:

As part of our commitment to user’s privacy and right to access, we give users transparency and control over their data. Users may create an account on the website, which allows them to view and manage their profile, preferences, and recent activity. You may also correct or update your information which can be found by using the “Profile and Preferences” link located in the footer throughout the site. 

### Modify And Opt Out:

You may modify the frequency or opt-out of the email newsletter by emailing us. There is also an option to modify or unsubscribe within every newsletter and by selecting “Profile and Preferences” located in the footer throughout the site.

You may cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services. In addition, you may also request that your personal information be erased. This ensures your “right to be forgotten”. We will only retain and use your information as necessary to comply with legal regulations.

To unsubscribe, cancel your account, or have your information erased, email us at [privacy@dunhilltraveldeals.com](mailto:privacy@dunhilltraveldeals.com).

### Online Forms:

If you choose to communicate with us via the Contact Us form, we will ask for a name, email address and phone number. We use this information to contact you regarding your specific concern.

If you choose to communicate with us via the Advertise with Us form, we will ask for your company name, a name, email address and phone number. We use this information to contact you regarding your interest in advertising on our site.

If you choose to use our Refer a Friend form, we will ask you for the name and email of yourself and your friend. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the website. We store this information for the purpose of sending this email and tracking the success of our referral program.

You may contact us at [privacy@dunhilltraveldeals.com](mailto:privacy@dunhilltraveldeals.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

### Cookies & Related Technology:

Dunhill Travel Deals uses “cookies” when you visit our website to track page requests and visitor preferences. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. The use of cookies allows us to provide our visitors with tailored content for that visitor’s preferences and interests. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept cookies, your experience at our website may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. We may also use pixel tags, which are tiny graphic images, in email messages to tell us whether emails have been opened to assure that we are only sending messages that are of interest to our users.

In addition, Dunhill Travel Deals automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including, but not limited to, your IP address, cookie information, browser information and the website page you requested. Dunhill Travel Deals uses this information for system administration and to examine our website traffic in aggregate. The information collected is used to improve the content of our web pages and to customize content for each user.

Please note that Dunhill Travel Deals may allow third party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Third party advertisers, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to our website and other websites. Individual user click behavior is not shared with third parties in ways other than disclosed in this privacy statement. Advertisers’ use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the Dunhill Travel Deals Privacy Policy.

### Display Advertising:

Dunhill Travel Deals or one of our web advertising partners may deliver ads appearing on the website to users of our website. Our web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers only the use of cookies by Dunhill Travel Deals and does not cover the use of cookies by any third party advertisers.

### Sharing With Third Parties:

Dunhill Travel Deals does not rent, share, sell, or trade your personal information with third parties other than as disclosed within this privacy policy.

From time to time, Dunhill Travel Deals may share your personal information within our family of brands. This sharing enables us to provide you with additional travel related products which might interest you. All brands follow practices that are at least as restrictive as those described in this Privacy Policy. There is an option to unsubscribe or modify your information within every brand’s newsletters and on each website

If Dunhill Travel Deals is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choice you may have regarding your personal information.

Dunhill Travel Deals may disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

### Outside Links:

Dunhill Travel Deals contains links to other sites. Dunhill Travel Deals is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. Dunhill Travel Deals encourages our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

### Security:

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow the highest industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. As such, we are not responsible for personally identifiable information that you may choose to share through these channels.

### International Regulations:

Dunhill Travel Deals has worked hard to make sure our policies and practices meet the highest standards for data privacy introduced by Canada’s Anti-Spam Law (CASL) and the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).  For all inquiries related to CASL or GDPR, please email [dataprotection@dunhilltraveldeals.com](mailto:dataprotection@dunhilltraveldeals.com) for assistance and information.

### Changes to our Policy:

Dunhill Travel Deals reserves the right to add to or modify this Policy simply by posting such addition or modification on the Dunhill Travel Deals website. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email or via a prominent notice on our site.

### Questions:

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [privacy@dunhilltraveldeals.com](mailto:privacy@dunhilltraveldeals.com).

Dunhill Travel Deals is proud to provide the highest level of privacy and we hope you'll find these updates improve your overall experience. Thank you for being a part of our community!
